Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
M_I_SForEver
Quiet out here.
Peaceful.
No Noise except my own.
Again, Manchee? Just go.
You don't have to ask me
every time
you wanna take a shit.
Crawlers.
I love that knife.
Poo and eat, it's all you do.
Manchee, come on.
Cursed.
Shit. Preacher.
Cursed is the ground
because of you.
Nobody goes
to church anymore.
Shut up,
control your Noise.
Control your Noise, Todd.
I am Todd Hewitt.
Think of something else,
think of something different.
- Think of birds.
- Dust you are...
Preacher.
To dust
you will return.
Why is the preacher here?
We don't even need a preacher.
Nobody goes to church anymore.